kidswb.com 2015-11-07

# Privacy | Kids WB

**CHILDREN'S PRIVACY POLICY**

Our visitors’ privacy is important to us at Warner Bros. Entertainment Group (“we,” “us,” “our”). We are providing this summary of our information practices (“Privacy Policy”) because we are committed to helping our visitors understand what personal information is collected on our online and mobile websites, services, and applications (“Site” or “Sites”) and to teaching visitors how to exercise control over this information while exploring our Sites. 

This Privacy Policy governs the collection and use of personal information at our Sites where this policy is posted. Some portions of the Sites may be directed at and may collect personal information from parents, teens, or other adults. In some cases, these sections may be subject to separate or additional privacy notices, such as our general [Warner Bros. Privacy Policy](http://www.warnerbros.com/privacy/policy.html) or another notice presented at the point of data collection.

**TRUSTe PRIVACY SEAL**  
Some of our Sites have been awarded TRUSTe’s Children’s Privacy Seal signifying that our practices on those Sites, along with this Privacy Policy, have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe’s program requirements](http://www.truste.com/products-and-services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements#Child) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of visitors’ personal information. For a list of Sites that are TRUSTe certified, please click here. 

TRUSTe’s mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy Trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If visitors have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us using the contact information below.  If not satisfied with our response, visitors can contact [TRUSTe here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint).

**THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT  **  
**Personal Information and Account Registration**. To enable visitors to participate in some of our online and mobile activities, or for us to respond to their requests, we may ask them to provide us with certain information, such as their first name, hometown, and an email address. For other activities that include enhanced interactive features, such as virtual worlds where visitors can play games, chat with their friends, and redeem virtual items or currency, we may require the child to choose a screen name and/or create an account with us. This account may require additional information, such as a username, password, and other profile information. 

**Parents, Guardians, Adults and Teens**. For certain activities on our Site and where a visitor indicates to us that he or she is a child, we may collect information about the visitor’s parent or guardian, such as the email address of the parent or guardian. We may use this information to:  (1) let the parent or guardian know of the child’s interest in the activity; (2) ask for the parent or guardian’s permission for the child to participate in that activity; (3) provide instructions to the parent or guardian on how to register and activate certain features of their child’s account; or (4) store the parent or guardian’s email in “hashed” or protected format (e.g., translated into a string of letters or numbers that don’t identify the individual) to help with account maintenance, such as to retrieve a lost password. On certain portions of a Site with activities directed to our adult and teen visitors, we may collect additional information from them such as a full name, address, email address, telephone number, or other information related to the activity. Similarly, certain portions of a Site may permit adults and teens to participate in interactive features that involve third parties, such as sharing content via social media accounts, interacting with social media plugins, or logging on via other third party platform accounts. When an adult or teen uses such social media platforms and plugins, some social media account information may be shared with us, such as a user name and other profile information. 

**Purchases and Transactions**. We may also offer parents and other adult visitors the opportunity to make purchases, such as a membership privileges,  virtual items and currency for use within our Sites and online games, merchandise, or gifts for themselves, friends or family, or to enable participation in certain interactive features. In such cases, we may require the parent or adult to provide a full name, billing and mailing addresses, email address, telephone number, and a credit card number. For orders shipped to a third party, we will also need the recipient’s name and mailing address. On occasion, we might solicit additional voluntary information regarding shoppers’ personal shopping preferences. Purchase transactions involving a credit card charge should be completed by a parent or guardian and are governed by our general [Warner Bros. Privacy Policy](http://www.warnerbros.com/privacy/policy.html).

**Communicating with Others**. On some areas of our Sites, visitors may want to communicate with their friends or tell their friends about our Site, so we may ask them to provide personal information about other people. This is usually limited to a first name and email address.  This information is used solely to respond to the visitor’s request and is deleted from our system once the message is sent.  Some Sites allow visitors to chat with friends in a way that displays their communications to other users of the Site.  These Sites generally allow child visitors to select pre-populated phrases or otherwise make use of tools or processes to filter and monitor chat messages written by the visitor.  If these tools detect personal information that a child visitor is trying to post personal information online, we will take reasonable measures to delete this personal information from the child’s postings before they are made public.

**Device and Usage Information**. We also collect certain information automatically when visitors use our Sites, such as the type of computer, device, mobile operating system (e.g., Windows or Mac OS) and browser (e.g., Firefox, Internet Explorer, mobile Internet browser) used to access our Site, mobile carrier, domain name of the Internet service provider (e.g., AT&T, Earthlink), certain identifiers (such as unique device identifier, IP address, and mobile device IP address), usage information (such as page requests and average time spent on our Site) and other information described in this Policy to help us support the internal operations of the Site.  See also the COOKIES AND OTHER TECHNICAL INFORMATION section below.

**Push Notifications**. Visitors may choose to receive push notifications from a mobile app. Visitors can always manage their push notification preferences at any time by adjusting the settings for the app on their mobile device.

**Contact Us**.  If a visitor chooses to contact us via email or through a customer support form, we may ask for certain personal information, such as name and email address and information regarding the inquiry.  Once we have fulfilled the visitor’s request, we will delete the personal information.

**HOW WE USE INFORMATION COLLECTED ON THE SITE  **  
**Providing our Products and Services**. In addition to providing our products, programs, and services, and any other purposes described in this Privacy Policy or at the time the information is collected, we also use visitors’ information in connection with activities for other internal purposes, such as to enable them to subscribe to our online newsletter, to enter one of our sweepstakes or contests, to express their opinions on various topics, to play games and communicate with their friends, and to offer other features, products, programs, and services that we believe may be of interest. We also use the information that we collect to support our internal operations, including personalizing content and experiences for Site visitors, improving and personalizing the design and content of our Sites, and analyzing site usage. We may use the information we collect to prevent potentially illegal or offensive activities or to enforce our rights or the rights of other visitors or third parties. We also may use the information pursuant to appropriate consent.

**HOW WE SHARE INFORMATION COLLECTED ON THE SITE  **  
**Service Providers**. Sometimes we use agents, contractors, or other service providers to provide services on our behalf to our visitors, such as providing visitors with virtual currency they may have purchased, redeeming points for virtual items or products, sending merchandise visitors have ordered, sending emails on our behalf, or helping us administer and fulfill prizes for a promotion, contest, or sweepstakes. In these cases, we require service providers to protect the confidentiality and security of the personal information. We may also use service providers for activities in support of internal operations, such as to perform analytics. 

**Co-Sponsors**. Some of our Sites, or portions of our Sites, may be co-sponsored by one or more of our business partners who may also collect or have access to visitors’ personal information. If this is the case, we will provide a notice at a point where the personal information is collected on the Site or upon download of the mobile app. 

**External Links**. Our Sites may contain links to third party websites, services, and applications whose information practices may be different from ours. Following these links may take the visitor to third party websites, services, and applications that may offer content or games, or conduct contests or sweepstakes that are separate from our Sites. If visitors are interested in these third party offerings, they should consult the privacy notices for the relevant third party, since those websites, services, and applications are not covered by our Privacy Policy and may follow different procedures. 

**Interactive Features for Teens and Adults**. When teen or adult visitors use social media platforms and third-party plugins on our Sites, the third parties who provide those features may be able to collect and use information about the visitor and activity on our Sites, including notifying the visitor's connections on the social media platform, in accordance with their own privacy policies. We recommend that visitors review these third-party privacy policies for more information about their information practices.

**Legal Process, Law Enforcement, and Corporate Transactions**. We and our agents, contractors, and service providers may disclose information we maintain when required to do so by applicable US or other law, for example, in response to a court order, subpoena, legal process, or other claim or inquiry. We also may disclose such information in response to a US or other law enforcement agency’s request or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the rights, property, or physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use, and to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Sites and applicable laws, or as otherwise required or permitted by US or other law or legal requirements. In addition, we may transfer information about our visitors in the event of a business transaction, such as if we or one of our business units or our relevant assets are acquired by, sold to, or merged with another company. 

**With Consent**. We may disclose visitors’ information for any other purposes pursuant to appropriate consent or at their direction.

**COOKIES AND OTHER TECHNICAL INFORMATION**  
**Cookies**. At some pages of our Sites, we, our service providers, and other third parties may use a software technology called “cookies” or similar technologies to support and enhance visitors’ online experiences. We place cookies on a visitor’s computer browser or device when they visit our Site so we can store their preferences and analyze their use of the Site, such as how many times someone visits our Sites and various sections of those Sites.  

Some of our Sites may use locally stored objects (sometimes referred to as “Flash cookies”) for Adobe’s Flash player and similar applications, in order to provide certain content, such as video on demand, video clips, or animation. This technology may also remember settings, such as screen size or font selection. Flash cookies are not managed through a visitor’s web browser, but Flash management tools can be accessed from [Adobe’s web site](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html). 

**Other Tracking Technologies**. We, our service providers, and other third parties also may use clear gifs (a.k.a. “web beacons”), images, or scripts placed on a web page or device to collect data, such as the number of visitors to a web page or app, or to deliver a cookie or other content to a visitor’s browser or device.

**Choices Regarding Cookies and Tracking Technologies**. For more information about cookies and how browser settings can be changed to reject them, visitors should go to their Site browser’s Help menu.  If a visitor decides not to accept cookies from our Sites, that visitor may not be able to take advantage of all of the features of our Site.  By using the Sites without rejecting cookies and similar online technologies, visitors consent to our use of such technologies to collect and process information. We do not currently take actions to respond to Do Not Track signals because a uniform technological standard has not yet been developed. We continue to review new technologies and may adopt a standard once one is created.

Google Analytics, one of our service providers, provides its own opt-out process. Visitors can find out more information about Google Analytics’ cookies [here](https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage). Visitors can control the use of Google Analytics relating to their use of our Sites, by downloading an installing the browser-plug in available [here](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en). 

**INTERNATIONAL TRANSFER  **  
We operate globally, so it may be necessary to transfer any information we collect via these Sites internationally. In particular, the information provided will likely be transferred to and processed in the United States by us, our agents or service providers. The data protection and other laws of other countries, such as the United States, may not be as comprehensive as those in the visitor’s home country. By using this Site, visitors consent to the collection, international transfer, storage, and processing of their information as set forth in this Privacy Policy and any other privacy notice provided at the time the information is collected. 

**OUR COMMITMENT TO SECURITY  **  
We maintain procedures intended to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the personal information we collect at our Sites.  Personal information collected at the Sites will not be stored for longer than is reasonably necessary for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy or at the time the information is collected or for the purposes of complying with our legal obligations, resolving disputes, enforcing our agreements, or responding to visitor requests.

**CHOICES; QUESTIONS; CONTACT US  **  
Visitors, including parents and guardians of child visitors, with questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy or who would like to review or update personal information collected on the Sites, have this information deleted, or request that there be no further collection, use, or disclosure of this information can contact us using the information below. 

If a visitor no longer wishes to have information collected by an application installed on the mobile device, they may uninstall the application by using the standard uninstall processes available on the mobile device or via the mobile application marketplace or network.

Warner Bros. Advanced Digital Services, a division of Warner Bros. Technical Operations Inc.   
Attention: Chief Privacy Officer   
4000 Warner Blvd., Bldg. 168, Burbank, CA 91522   
Telephone: (818) 977-0018   
Email: [privacy@wb.com](mailto:privacy@wb.com) 

**NOTIFICATION REGARDING UPDATES  **  
From time to time, we may update this Privacy Policy. We will notify Site visitors about material changes to our privacy practices by placing a notice on the Site where this Privacy Policy is posted or by sending the parent or guardian an email message. We encourage visitors to periodically check back to review this policy to understand our current privacy practices. 

Date Updated: March 13, 2014  

Warner Bros. Entertainment Group companies that agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy may access the information collected from users on our Web site (even from users based in a different territory) and may use that information for the purposes described in our Privacy Policy. Below is a list of some of the Warner Bros. Entertainment Group companies that currently may market to our users in this way. We may update this list from time-to-time, so please check back periodically to keep up-to-date. 

DC Entertainment  
Flixster, Inc.  
New Line Productions, Inc.  
Telepictures Production Inc.  
TMZ Productions Inc.  
Turbine, Inc.  
WB Games Inc.  
Warner Bros. Advanced Digital Services, a division of Warner Bros. Technical Operations Inc.  
Warner Bros. Animation Inc.  
Warner Bros. Consumer Products Inc.  
Warner Bros. Digital Distribution, a division of Warner Bros. Home Entertainment Inc.  
Warner Bros. Distributing Inc.  
Warner Bros. Entertainment Inc.  
Warner Bros. Interactive Entertainment, a division of Warner Bros. Home Entertainment Inc.  
Warner Bros. International Television Distribution Inc.  
Warner Bros. Pictures, a division of WB Studio Enterprises Inc.  
Warner Bros. Studio Facilities, a division of WB Studio Enterprises Inc.  
Warner Bros. Television Distribution Inc.  
Warner Bros. Television, a division of WB Studio Enterprises Inc.  
Warner Bros. Television Group  
Warner Home Video, a division of Warner Bros. Home Entertainment Inc.

Below is a list of some of the Time Warner companies that are affiliated with the Warner Bros. Entertainment Group companies and with whom we may share information we collect at our Sites. We may update this list from time-to-time with additional Time Warner companies, so please check back periodically to keep up-to-date.

Cartoon Network  
Home Box Office  
Time Inc.  
Turner Broadcasting System  

The following online and mobile websites, services, and applications have been awarded TRUSTe’s Children’s Privacy Seal for compliance with [TRUSTe’s program requirements](http://www.truste.com/products-and-services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements#Child).

chimaonline.com  
LEGO Legends of Chima mobile application
